

CONTACT INFORMATION:

Email:

sadiqueah@outlook.com
sadiqueah@live.com

Mob: +971 501656141

LinkedIn:

sadique-hakim-007

SKILLS:

- Confidence
- > Time Management
- Friendliness and manners
- > Ambition
- > Focus
- Situational Awareness
- > Enthusiasm
- Optimism
- Empathy.

Sadique A H

Objective:

Cluster Assistant IT Manager with 10 years of experience in Hospitality sector, is now looking forward to playing a leading role in developing and monitoring the best Industrial practice in your company operations. Pursue the goal of no harm to people and the environment by developing a continuous auditing and monitoring program.

Education:

Mahatma Gandhi University
 Kerala, India.
 Bachelor of Science
 BSc Computer Science.

Certification & Courses

- ➤ Networking-CCNA Certification (CISCO ID: CSCO12471769)
- WINDOWS 7,10, SERVER 2012, 2016 R2 MCTS (Microsoft Certified) (MC ID: 10299386)
- ➤ COMPUTER HARDWARE & NETWORKING (ICES Certified)
- ➤ WINDOWS XP, SERVER 2003 M.C.P (Command IT Solutions)
- ➤ BASIC COMPUTER COURSE (MS OFFICE Chain Computers)
- ➤ Mobile Technology (M.I.T Certified)

Professional and Technical Skills

- Communication and interpersonal skills
- Problem Solving and Decision Making
- Organisation and Time Management, Strategic Thinking
- > Financial management, Project Management, Risk Management
- Conflict Resolution, Collaboration
- ➤ Self-development Skills.
- ➤ Computer and Digital Literacy

Profile Highlights

- Experience in working as Cluster Assistant IT Manager.
- ➤ Being Asst.IT Manager taking care of all IT operations.
- > Providing proper handover to Regional IT manager on daily basis.
- Data center monitoring on daily basis.
- ➤ Being IT Manager supervising the day-to-day activities of a team.
- ➤ Being IT Manager dealing with vendors for follow up, support and maintenance.
- ➤ Keep and maintain proper inventory.
- Follow ups for all maintenance and AMC renewal.
- > Driving operational efficiencies, raising customer service levels.
- > Organizing workload, allocating tasks, tasking team on a daily basis.
- Managing team and individual performance.
- Ensuring all administrative records are completed accurately.
- Ensure professionalism & high quality is continually maintained.
- Preparation of relevant reports and documents for senior managers.
- ➤ Identifying areas of the business where improvements can be made.
- Developing policies to create and maximize performance.
- > Scheduling staffing levels, planning for holiday and weekend cover.
- Monitoring staff attendance and performance levels
- > Opening and closing the office premises.
- Involved in the recruitment & interviewing of new staff.
- > Training of new staff & identifying training requirements of existing staff.
- Ensuring compliance with all relevant health and safety guidelines
- Monitoring, managing and troubleshooting
- ➤ Handling system administration task like user account management, software installation, backup and hardware troubleshooting etc.

PROFESSIONAL BACKGROUND:

December 2019-Now

Working as Cluster Assistant IT Manger, handling Data Management in Danat Jebel Dhanna Resort and Dhafra Beach Hotel under NCT&H, Jebel Dhanna, Ruwais, Abu Dhabi, UAE. My job responsibilities are:

- Managing and maintaining Microsoft Windows applications and systems.
- Assisting with the maintenance of the hotel's local area network hardware/software and network operations to include:
 - Troubleshooting connectivity problems;
 - Installing and maintaining routers;
 - Adding/terminating users;
 - Assigning rights and access;
 - Assessing and reporting operational status;
 - Performing backups and restores;
 - Including performing routine preventative maintenance.
- ➤ Providing Training in different Softwares such as Opera, Sun, FBM, Simphony, Touche, FMC, Oasis, PayTrax, PABX, CCTV etc.
- Establishing, documents, tests and communicates short-term and long-termemergency procedures.
- > Ensuring technology documents/certificates such as product registrations, SSL certificates, maintenance agreements, service contracts etc. related to technology operations and or technology services are evaluated; updated; and processed.
- ➤ Ensuring compliance with all software licensing agreements and safeguardssoftware media and associated licenses.
- ➤ Implements, administrates and maintains databases.
- ➤ Ensuring that all company IT related Standard Operating Procedures are implemented, monitored and updated accordingly.
- > Implementing technological alternatives to streamline functions and improve productivity.
- Maintaining and testing the technology disaster recovery plan.
- Ensuring networks, workstations, operating system and software applications are operational; ensures hardware and software is patched and or updated; ensures all analog and broadband circuits are operational in accordance with vendor specifications. Responsible for troubleshooting workstations, networks, software applications, phones, copiers and other technologies.
- ➤ Demonstrates the 12-Service Excellence Basics and ensure the whole of theIT department continually follows the same.
- Updating the latest industry trends to be able to make recommendations to upgrade existing systems and new product in themarket.
- Providing feedback on performance for the purpose of performance evaluations regarding colleague probation periods, annual performance reviews promotion or transfer consideration and salary reviews.
- Establishes comprehensive training programmes for thedepartment.
- Responsible for deployment and maintaining HSIA including WiFi where appropriate, as per brand requirements in order to generate revenue to thehotel.
- ➤ Compiling the annual IT budget in line with recommended upgrades tooperating systems and equipment.
- Actively participates in all hotel energy saving and recycling initiatives.
- Attends monthly departmental meetings and daily briefings as required
- Ensuring self and all IT department colleagues actively participate in all OSHMS and FSMS (HACCP) requirements.
- Actively participates and involved in all Occupational Health and Safety requirements and ensure that all Manager follow the same.
- Accountable to make sure that the subordinates are following the Occupational Health and Safety standards inline with OSHAD requirements.

Other Experience

No	Term	Organisation	Job Title
1	08.12.2019 to Now	Danat Jebel Dhanna Resort (5 Star) & Dhafra Beach Hotel (3 Star) (Preopening)	Cluster Assistant IT Manger
2	22.11.2015 to 04.12.2019	Radisson Blu – 4 Star & Parkinn by Radisson 3 Star – Abu Dhabi (Yas Plaza Hotels)	Cluster IT Supervisor
3	31.12.2013 to 15.11.2015	THE H Dubai – Luxury 5 Star Property	IT Specialist
4	02.01.2012 to 25.12.2013	Coral Beach Resort Sharjah – 4 Star Property & BAHI AJMAN PALACE – 5 Star (Preopening)	IT Administrative Assistant
5	(2009 – 2011)	CHAIN COMPUTERS Attingal & Thiruvananthapuram , India	System Engineer & Networking Associate

POINTS FOR SELF: -

- Good command over English Language.
- > Skills in decision making
- Ability to forecasts the problems that may occur in the system.
- ➤ Accustom myself to the changes
- ➤ Hard working, loyal, accommodative, and adaptive.
- > Extrovert personality.
- > Strongly believe in team work.
- > Perceiving my carrier with optimism.
- > Interested in gaining up-to-date knowledge on Information Technology.

REFERENCE

Mr. Renjith Chandran General Manager Danat Jebel Dhanna Resort & Dhafra Beach Hotel Jebel Dhanna, Ruwais, Abu Dhabi

Mob: +971 55 895 7645

Email: renjith.chandran@danathotels.com.

Mr. Rufaik Malik Cluster IT Manager Yas Plaza Hotels (Radisson Blu & Parkinn Yas Island) Abu Dhabi

Mob: +971 56 619 7734

Email: rufaik.malik@yasplazahotels.com